（三木）ふっ…。
（古市）三木！
Miki...
ふっ。
（男鹿）ふっ。
久しぶりだね　男鹿。
It's been a long time, Oga.
驚いたよ　まさかこんな形で
また君に会えるなんて…。→
I'm surprised that we'd meet again like this.
男鹿君
君も　もちろん来るよね。
You'll be sure to come, Oga-kun, won't you?
つ～か　さっきから
馴れ馴れしいんだけど…。
It's weird. You're acting like you know me...
お前　誰だっけ？
（ベル坊）アイ　アイ！ガルルル…。
Who are you, again?
う～っ！
はいっ！
うっ！
あっ…。
あっ　あっ…。
（邦枝）男鹿！
アイ～！
Oga!
頭に来るね　その物言い。
ただの天邪鬼か　本心か…。
The way you talk really pisses me off.
Is it just you being contrary, or is
that really who you are? Either way.
どっちにしろ　君はそうやって
仲間を突き放す。→
That's the way you push away your friends.
人の信頼を
簡単に踏みにじるんだ！
You step on people's trust
like it was nothing!
めりこみパーンチ！
Burying Punch!
パーンチ！パーンチ！
パーンチ！パーンチ！！
Punch! Punch! Punch!
めりこみキーック！
Punch!
Burying Kick!
本当の必殺技が　どういうものか
見せてあげるよ。
I'll show you what a real special attack is.
（三木）
最初に言っておく。
この技は　手加減が出来ない。→
I'll tell you this ahead of time...
I can't hold back with this technique.
当たればいくら君でも
ただでは済まないだろう。
If it hits, even you won't escape unhurt.
だから…絶対にかわすんだよ！
So you'd better make sure to dodge it!
（静）そこまで。
あっ…。
That's far enough.
男鹿…次だ。次こそ叩き潰す。
Oga... Next time. Next time I'll crush you.
ぬかせ　バーカ！
Get lost, idiot.
え～いっ！
ハァ…ハァ…。
（三木）あと　少し…。
Just a little longer...
（由加）みんな！学園祭の競技が
決まったっス！
Everyone, the competition during the
school festival's been decided on!
（姫川）ほ～う。
それで？
Oh?
（涼子）はい。
バレーボールっス。
And?
Right...
It's volleyball.
バレーボール…。
Volleyball?
（姫川・東条・神崎）バレーボール…。
Volleyball...
（一同）バレーボール！
Volleyball!
There Are Wounds in the Past.
（姫川）はぁ～～っ！！
フー　まあまあだな。うっ…。
Not bad, I suppose.
（神崎）
てっめえ
ふざけんてじゃね～ぞ　こら！
Stop foolin' around, you bastard!
あぁ！？
（神崎）なんだよ
そのサラッサラは！！→
What the hell's with the flowing locks, eh?
姫川はもっとこう…モサッとして
ヌメッとしてんだよ！
Himekawa's more like, poofy, or silky!
てめ～らが言うから
こ～したんだろうが！あぁ！？
It's this way 'cause you assholes complained!
Yeah?!
あぁじゃねえよ！
ムカつくんだよ色々と～！！
Don't "yeah" me!
Yer pissin' me off in all kinds o' ways!
あんだとコラーッ！
うわっ！！
Say that again, punk!
騒がない！
とっととポジションにつく！
No arguing!
Get back in your positions!
（神崎・姫川）へ～い。
古市ちょっと。
なんだ？
'Kay...
Furuichi, may I have a sec?
What is it?
いいから来いや！！
オレ…何してんの？
Whatever, get over here!
What am I doing?
（邦枝）≪ほら　もう１回いくわよ≫
（神崎・姫川）≪へ～い≫
Okay, we're going to try this again!
'Kay...
いや　何って…。
"What", you ask?
だって！
お前　考えたらおかしいだろ！？
Stop to think about it! This isn't right!
オレは　あのチビを
ぶっとばしてぇだけなんだよ！
I just wanna beat the crap outta that shrimp!
なのに何だ　バレーボールって！
ダ～？
So why the hell am I playing volleyball?
別におかしかね～よ。
It's not really strange...
バレーボール勝負で負けたら
退学ってことになってるし…。
If you lose the volleyball
match, you'll be expelled.
バカヤロウ！
あ～！なぜっ！？
You idiot!
Why?
目を覚ませ　古市！
アブダッ！
Open your eyes, Furuichi!
覚めてるよ！
ってか閉じかけたよ！
They're open!
Or more like half closed now!
オレはケンカがしてぇんだ！
退学なんてど～でもいいじゃない。
I wanna fight!
Who gives a crap about being expelled?!
いいわけね～だろ！！
お前が目ぇ覚ませ！
You should!
Open your eyes!
やだやだやだ…
ケンカしたいよ～！
ダッダッダッ…。
No, no, no, no, no!
I wanna fight!
ケンカケンカケンカ…。
ダッダッダッ…。
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
駄々こねんな！そこっ！
Cut the tantrum!
You there!
（ズバァーン）
お？
おっ？
ニョ。
何の音だ？
ダ？
What's that sound?
（サンドバッグが揺れる音）
ダ～。
ふぉ～。
よう！そいつが例の必殺技か？
Hey. Was that the special
move you were talking about?
オレでいっちょ試してみろや。
（三木）男鹿？
Let me test it out for ya.
Oga?
アブ～。
残像だ。
何が？
An afterimage...
What is?
《おいおいおい
今ケンカなんかしたら…》
Come on now... If you
fight or something now...
え？
なんだこれ？
What's this?
（三木）
着な。ケンカじゃなく
手合わせなら問題ないだろ？
Put this on.
It's no problem if we're sparring
instead of fighting, yes?
僕もバレーの練習に
うんざりしてたところだ。→
I've gotten bored with
volleyball practice myself.
お望み通り　見せてやるよ。→
I'll show you, just as you wish...
出馬八神流の奥義を…。
The Secret Technique of the
Izuma Eight Gods Style!
（静）三木君　こっそり
練習してるみたいだけど…。→
It looks like Miku-kun is
practicing in secret...
いいの？放っておいて。
You sure about leaving him alone?
（出馬）う～ん　１回見せたんが
アカンかったかなぁ？→
Yeah... I showed it to him.
Maybe I shouldn't have...
正直あいつには
早すぎる技なんやけど。→
Honestly, it's a technique
he's not ready for yet.
おおっ！あ～。練習やめさすのは
どうやったって無理や。
But there was no way I could have
stopped him from practicing...
え！
ふ～。
アホみたいに強さに
執着しとるんや。あいつは…。
The guy's obsessed with becoming
stronger. Acting like a fool...
うしっ！
アブ！
Okay!
Begin!
（三木）用意はいいかい？
おう！いつでもいいぜ。
Are you ready?
Yeah! Anytime...
奥義とやらを
ガツンと打ってこいや！
Give me your best shot with
this secret technique.
ン・ン・ン…。ダー！
Begin!
（三木）
相変わらずだね　後悔するよ。
ダー！
You never change, do you?
You'll regret it.
Be...gin!
あの時　どうして僕を裏切った？
あ？
Why did you betray me back then?
とぼけるな！３年前だ。
Don't play dumb.
Three years ago. At the end of
our first year of middle school.
中学１年の終わり。
ダー！！
落ち着け！ベル坊！
Calm down, Baby Beel!
（三木）君を倒す前に
聞いておきたいと思ってね。
I wanted to ask you, before I defeat you.
回想
（古市）転校？マジで！？えっ　いつ？
Transfer? Really?
When?
（三木）うん。春休みに入ったら→
Yeah... I'm going to my
mother's house in the spring.
お母さんの実家の方に行くんだ。
奈良だって。
In Nara.
奈良かぁ～マジかよ。
超遠いじゃん。
Nara? Really?
That's really far away...
大仏のいるところな。知ってる。
なんで誇らしい気！？
Oh, I know that place. With the Big Buddha!
Why are you acting proud to know that?
ハフッ。
あ～！！てめえ　人の取って
食ってんじゃねぇ～よ！
Hey, don't just eat other people's food!
（三木の声）
２人とは　クラスが違うけど
それでも知り合って数ヵ月。→
The two of us were in different classes,
and it was only a few months
we'd known each other...
一緒にいるのは
本当に楽しかった。→
But the time we spent
together was really fun.
だからこの先　離れても
ずっと友達だと思っていた。
So I thought we'd continue to be
friends, even if we moved apart.
（不良）あぁ？なんだ　てめえ？
Huh? What's yer problem?
か　返して下さい。
そのお守り。
（不良）こらっ　てめえ！
Please give that charm back!
You little punk!
（霧矢）ああ…これ？ほらよ。→
Oh, this?
Here... Oopsie, it slipped out of my hand...
あ～らら。手がすべっちまった。→
あ～らら　足もすべっちまった。
Oopsie, my foot slipped too...
やめろ！
キモいんだよ！クソが。
Stop it!
You're makin' me sick, you wimp.
（不良）
お～っと　大人しくしろ！
Now play nice!
（ドカァーン）
≪うわぁ≫
≪ぐわっ≫
あ？
（不良達）あぁ…。
よお…こいつら友達？
Hey...
Are these guys your pals?
（不良）≪男鹿！？≫
（不良）≪硬中のアバレオーガだ！！≫
Oga?!
It's the Rampaging Ogre from Kata Middle!
落しもん探すんなら　手伝おうかと
思ったけど…必要か？
I was thinking of helping to
look for something you dropped,
You need help with that?
いや…１人で充分だよ。
No... I'll be fine by myself.
フン。
返せよ！
あ？
Give it back!
なんだそりゃ。
爆笑　誘ってんのか？
What's this? Are you trying to make me laugh?
僕のお守りから
その足をどけろっ！！
Get your foot off my charm!
うっ…。
てめ～が男鹿か。来いよ。
てめ～も　こいつの餌食だ。
So, you're Oga?
Come on. You'll fall prey
to this hand as well.
フン　どこ見てんだよ。
Where are you looking?
あ？おっ…てめえっ！
Huh?
Why, you...
返せって…言ってんだろっ！！
I told you to give it back!
うわぁ～！おっとっと！？
（霧矢）え　あと　と…
あああの　あ　あ～→
Um...
あ～～！！
（三木）このお守り
父さんに貰ったんだ。→
I got that charm from my dad.
うちの両親　離婚するんだけど…
僕は　母さんについていくから。
My parents are divorced, see, and
I'm going to live with my mother.
ふ～ん　それで転校か。
（古市）つうか　その傷　大丈夫？
Oh, so that's why you're transferring.
Anyway, is that wound okay?
（三木）
うん。別にどうってことないよ。
It's nothing much...
((根性あんじゃね～か))
You got guts.
へへ…。
へんな奴。
Weirdo...
（三木の声）
初めて君が
認めてくれた気がした。→
That's the first time I
felt you accepted me...
でもそれは
本当に　気がしただけだったんだ。
But it was just my imagination...
（生徒）
聞いた？魔野中の奴ら　男鹿君
追っかけまわしてるんだって。
Did you hear? Oga-kun went and did a
number on those guys from Mano Middle...
（生徒）聞いた　聞いた。
霧矢とかいう奴が→
I heard! That Kiriya guy vowed
revenge or something, right?
復讐すんでしょ？
蛇みたいに　しつこいって。
He's as persistent as a snake!
（三木）ハァハァハァ…男鹿君！
Oga-kun!
あ？
（三木）ボロボロじゃないか！→
You're all beat up!
どうして
言ってくれなかったんだ！→
Why didn't you tell me?
僕のせいだよ！
だから　僕もいっしょに！
It's my fault, right? So
we should go together!
つ～かさ　お前　誰だっけ？
So, yeah... Who are you, again?
かばってくれてんの？
Are you covering for me?
他人のふりして
巻き込まないように…。→
Pretending like we don't know each
other, so I don't get involved?
いいんだ。必要ないよ！
どうせあと→
It's okay! You don't have to do that!
I mean, I'm moving far away in a week anyway!
１週間もしないうちに
遠くへ引越しちゃうんだ。→
だから　最後くらい…。
（霧矢）≪男鹿～！！≫
So at least, until the end...
Oga!
でてこいやぁ～！
Get out here!
（不良）こいつが男鹿かぁ。
So, you're Oga!
（三木）《足手まといでもなんでも
僕は僕は　君と一緒に！》
Sure, I may get in your way,
but whatever happens...
I... I...
I'm going to be together with you!
（三木）待って　男鹿くん！
Wait, Oga-kun!
（バンッ）
（ドサッ）
うっ…。
馴れ馴れしいんだよ。
誰だ　お前？
You act like you know me.
Who are you?
な　なんで？
W-Why?
（ズカ！ドカ！）
すっこんでろ！
Get lost!
弱ぇくせに　目障りなんだよ！
（ズカ！ドカ！）
You're a weakling! Get outta my sight!
（三木）くっ…くっ…。
う…う…。
現在
ダ…ダブ…ダブダ。
Annoyed... Annoyed... Annoyed...
You don't intend to say anything, do you?
（三木）結局　何も
言うつもりはないんだね。→
まあいいさ。それならそれで…。
Well, fine.
To each his own, I suppose.
ダーダッ　ダブ…。
That's your answer.
（三木）それが君の答えだ。
Be...
Here I come!
いくぞ！
ダーブ！
Begin!
べ　ベル坊　おしかったぞ。
だから泣かないで…。
B-Baby Beel... You were
close! So, don't cry...
ど～したよ！？奥義を見せて
くれるんじゃなかったのかよ！？
What's wrong? Weren't you going
to show me your secret technique?
Izuma Eight Spirits Style...
Whirlwind Ax Kick!
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ
ふ～っ　あぶなかったぜ。
That was close!
Um, you took a direct hit.
いや　モロに喰らったろ　お前。
ぜ～んぜん！これっぽっちも
きいてねえよ　ハゲェ！
Not even close!
A tiny tap like that don't phase me, asswipe!
るらあ～！必殺めりこみキック！！
Special Move Burying Kick!
（三木）足元…。
Your feet...
（三木）出馬八心流…。
Izuma Eight Spirits
Style... Twin Palm Strike!
ぐっ！
After that, I vowed...
あれから僕は誓ったんだ…
絶対に強くなる。→
...to become stronger, no matter what!
I'd do anything no matter how hard...
その為なら　どんな努力も
惜しまないと…。
Izuma Eight Spirits Style... Twin Bind Fist!
（三木）出馬八心流…。
ぐ…！
♪♪～
（古市）
《す　すげえ。
あの男鹿が押されている…→
W-Whoa...
Oga is actually being pushed back!
Miki really did get strong!
三木のやつ
本当に強くなってる…》
チッ！
ハッ…きかねえなぁ。
I didn't feel it.
You really didn't think that
was gonna end it, did you?
まさか　それでしまいとか
ゆ～んじゃねえだろうな。
Man, that Tojo person and all you
delinquents are damn tough...
まったく…
あの東条とかいう人といい→
君達　不良のタフさには
あきれるよ…。→
安心しな　今からが本番だ。
Don't worry. The main event's about to start.
かわせ…とは　もう言わないよ。
I'm not gonna tell you to dodge it this time.
Is this it?
来るか…。
Izuma Eight Spirits Style...
Secret Technique!
Dark Death Warbler!
（ドキュオオン！）
（三木）この技は　まだ未完成だ…。
This technique is not yet perfected.
今で七割。
く…。
Currently about 70%...
Yeah, I held back some, but the main problem
was that my hands were already injured.
（三木）
威力も　もちろんそうだけど→
それ以上に僕の拳が
ダメージを受けている…。
I can't use them again for a little while.
《しばらくは
使い物にならないか…。→
It's harder than I thought to hit
a person of flesh and blood...
生身の人間にあてるのは
思った以上にむずかしい》
Man... I can't really call this a victory.
（三木）
まったく　これじゃあ
勝ったとは　とても言えないな。→
There're two weeks until the school festival.
学園祭までは　あと２週間。
出馬さんの話では→
According to what Izuma told me, after the
volleyball, there'll be a place for us to fight.
バレーボールの後に
僕らの試合の場もあるらしい。→
Before then, I'm going to
perfect this technique.
その時までに
僕はこの技を完成させる…。→
そして　きっちりと証明するよ。
And I'll show you once and for
all that I'm stronger than you!
僕の方が強いってことを…。
（由加）結局　男鹿っちと古市
戻ってきませんでしたね。
Oga and Furuichi never came back, did they?
Seriously... Get 'em together
and they split right back up.
（寧々）
ホント　まとまったと思ったら
すぐこれだもの。
いっぺん　しめた方が
いいっスよ～。
We should deal with those idiots...
でも　どこ行ったのかしら？
But, I wonder where they went?
They left with their gym clothes on, right?
体操服のまま
出て行ったんでしょ？
案外　六騎聖の誰かと
ケンカしてたりして…。
Maybe they fought with one
of the 6 Holy Knights...
Got the crap beat out of them...
（涼子）
んで　ボコボコにやられたり？
Don't kid about that. I know they're
stupid, but they aren't that stupid...
まさか　いくらあいつらでも
そこまでバカじゃないでしょ。
（チーン！）
（邦枝）あ…！
（由加）あ　ボロボロ。
They're all beat up.
Hold it, you people!
（邦枝）ちょっと　あんたたち！
Don't tell me you actually got in a fight!
まさか　本当に
ケンカしてたんじゃ。
（古市）すんません。
Sorry...
明日は　ちゃんと練習出ますんで→
We'll make sure to come
to practice tomorrow...
今日は　かんべんして下さい。
待てよ　男鹿！男鹿～！
Please forgive us for today!
Wait, Oga!
Oga!
Miki's gotten crazy strong...
（古市）
三木のやつ…
めちゃくちゃ強くなってたな。→
めちゃくちゃ
努力したんだろ～な。
He must have worked super hard...
（古市）いいんかよ
３年前のこと言わね～で。→
It's okay... There's no reason not to talk
about what happened three years ago, right?
別にもう問題ね～だろ。
Why?!
（三木）((なんで…))
関係ね～よ　んなこた。
It don't matter.
（男の子）ありがとう！
（東条）おう　まいどっ。
Thank you!
Sure, come again!
お…男鹿。
Oga!
How many jobs do you have?
てめえ　いくつバイトしてんだよ。
（東条）珍しい客だな…
何にするよ？
Now here's a rare customer...
What'll I do you for?
ケンカしようぜ。
（東条）ああ？
Let's fight.
そいつは…たけえぞ。
That's a pricey one...
Oh, yeah... The first time
we fought was around here...
（東条）
そ～いやあ　てめえと最初に
やりあったのも　この辺か…。→
So, what happened?
で　何があった？
てめえ…あのチビの技　喰らってもピンピンしてたな。
You were fine and dandy after
taking that shrimp's attack...
((このぉ！))
Why, you...
Crushing Fist!
((いてえじゃね～か))
That hurt.
あ？おいおい　お前まさか…。→
Wait, you're kidding me...
その傷　あのチビにやられたのか？
Did that shrimp give you those wounds?
んなわけね～だろ　ボケが！
O-Of course not, jerk!
これは　あれだ！虫歯だ！（東条）フッ　そ～かよ。
These came from... You know, a toothache!
Really?
そ～だよ。
そ～か。
Yeah, really.
I see.
そ～だっつってんだろ！！にょ！
I said it was a toothache!
（東条）そ～じゃあ
しっかたねえなあ～！
Well, no choice then!
ダブッ！
おいおい。
うん　うん。
Hey, whoa...
はっ！
（東条）もう２～３本→
I'll give you another 2 or 3 cavities!
虫歯にしてやるよ～！！
If I got a special move good
enough to take you down...
お前を倒せる必殺技がありゃ！
I can beat that guy!
あいつに勝てる！！
なんだそりゃ…。
Huh?
ぜんぜん　きかね～ぞ？→
It didn't hurt at all.
おめえ　弱くなったんじゃね～の？ああ？
Did you get weaker?
必殺技だのなんだのと
くだらねえ。→
Who gives a crap about
special moves or whatever...
All that matters is how
strong a guy's arm is!
要はこいつの強さだろ？
Oga!
男鹿！
ダーブ！
へ…こっちも全然　きかねえなぁ。
Looks like yours ain't hurtin' either...
ウソつけ…。
Liar.
フッ…。
ハハハハ。
フフハハハ。
ハハハハッ。
（東条・男鹿）フハハハッ！
（東条・男鹿）ワハハハハッ！
（ドカッ）
（東条・男鹿）ハーッハハハハ！
（ドカッ　ボカッ）
まったく　ついていけない世界だ…笑いながら殴りあってるよ…。
I'm not made for their world...
They're laughing while
punching each other out...
（東条・男鹿）アーッハハハハ！
（ドカッ　ボカッ）
ダブダッ！
Wait, Beel!
（東条）待てっ！ベル！！
てめえ　ひいきすんな！→
Don't call it!
Just look! Oga's clearly way more beat up!
よく見ろ！男鹿の方が確実に
ボロボロじゃね～か！
ダブー！
惜しかったな…。
テメーも
勝ち誇ってんじゃね～よ！
You came close...
Don't pretend like you've won!
ふん…行くぜ　ベル坊。
Let's go, Baby Beel.
にょ。
心配かけちまったな…
だが見えたぜ。
Sorry for worrying you...
But I can see clearly now.
My ultimate special move...
最強の必殺技…。
Well, have a look. Basically,
it's about fighting spirit.
まあ見てな。要は気合だ。
Next time I'll beat that shrimp
'til he's on his knees...
次こそはお望み通り　あのチビ
ガックガクにしてやるからよ。
バレーもケンカも　全部勝つぞ！！
アダァ！！
Volleyball, fighting... I'll win them all!
フッフフ。
ヘヘヘヘ…。
（出馬）あ　うう…あああ…→
あお～　いつもすまんなぁ
お静さん。→
Sorry about always asking
you for this, Oshizu-san...
ああっ！そこ効くわ～。
Ooh, that's the spot.
You're too tense. Go to a real chiropractor!
（静）こりすぎ！
ちゃんと整体行きなさい！
うおおっ！
あれさあ　羨ましくない？
Aren't you jealous?
I mean, isn't that hot?
つか　エロくない？
どう思うよ　みんなぁ！
（出馬）おお～っ。
What do you think, everyone?
It's finally the school festival
everyone's been waiting for!
It's time to finish things
with the 6 Holy Knights!
But before that, there's
something we must do.
Strategist, please help
us with our class's café!
Leave it to me!
For this day, I gathered data in Akihabara
and have taken pictures together with the maids!
A maid café?!
On the next Beelzebub: Maids Run Amok.
Now then, about next week, Azusa-kun...
Come again! (We've got maids!)